# Ivan Dimitrov

#### ABOUT

I am a backend software developer who enjoys working in a high energy environment using modern technologies. I am used to applying agile methodologies and breaking down user requirements. Some of the technologies used daily are GOlang, PostgreSQL, GraphQL and RESTFul services. I am familiar with git, docker, LaTeX and NoSQL databases as well. I am not afraid of making decisions and taking responsibility. I have also experience with enterprise projects using Java and Android.

## Professional EXPERIENCE

# StageAI, Sofia

Senior Software Developer

May 2020 - Present

- ▷ Solving complex tasks mainly using GOlang and PostgreSQL.
- ▶ Provide and help others to provide good quality code.
- $\triangleright$  Supervise the working processes applying agile methodologies.
- ▶ Breakdown tasks and requirements.

Software Developer

Jan 2018 - May 2020

- ▷ Developed various web application using mainly with GOlang, SQL and NoSQL DBs, REST and Graphql.
- ▷ Deliver high quality code.
- ▶ Enjoy doing tests, try to apply TDD.

#### Musala Soft, Sofia

Software developer

Aug 2016 - Dec 2017

▶ Worked as a contractor for Experian maintaining their existing project using mainly internal tools in the Java ecosystem.

Junoir Software Developer

Aug 2015 - Aug 2016

- ▶ Developed native android applications with Java.
- ▶ Maintained Java Enterprise application using JSP, maven, OracleDB.
- ▶ Maintained hybrid mobile application with Javascript and apache Cordova.

# Game developer-intern, Varna

Software Developer

Aug 2014 - Sept 2014

# SKILLS

Golang, PostgreSQL, GraphQL, RESTFul services.

#### **EDUCATION**

### Technical University, Varna

M.S of Computer Science Sep 2013 - June 2015 B.S of Electronics Sep 2009 - June 2013

#### CERTIFICATIONS Oracle Certified Professional, Oracle

Sep 2017

Agile Software Development, The Business Institute

Apr 2017

Managing Team Performance, The Business Institute

Feb 2017

Oracle Certified Associate, Oracle

Nov 2016